out that weapon but investigators had already told us one thing that we knew a few days ago was
that they found the rifle out wrapped in a towel right near the shooting scene so they had it but
what we didn't know was exactly how old it was and it's important to point that out because police
say the suspect might have chosen that gun because it was pretty much untraceable i want to show it
to you on your screen for people watching at home this is what that weapon looked like according to
authorities it's a mauser model vintage rifle that investigators say is so old they didn't even have
a serial number on it so they wouldn't have been able to track it down this is the weapon that
police say tyler robinson used to assassinate charlie kirk that day it dated back several decades the
gunman calling it grandpa's rifle you can begin by investigating the techniques of propaganda
glittering generalities what is a glittering generality a victory for good government but
it's true isn't it what's true what does good government mean is the mayor's idea of good
government the same as yours i think it's a glittering generality one of the best there's
another yes and why do you suppose our opponents chose that phrase i guess because everybody likes
a real american right and they wanted to transfer that liking for a real american to mr butler but a
great deal of propaganda is much more hidden much harder to detect you'll find that the purpose of
most propaganda is to persuade people to believe something to do something or to buy something your
next step and it's a big one is to get the facts well is he a real american howard butler was born in
this country he obeys its laws he's a good citizen yes he is a real american the same can be said for richard
mr cooper so ask yourself whether the facts support the purpose do they support the transfer of feeling
from real american to mr butler over mr cooper no i guess not well that's your fourth step weigh the
facts against the purpose and the technique i think i understand to know whether propaganda is good or not
whether it's true or not i should know the purpose recognize the technique get the facts and judge the
purpose and technique by the facts